Guide to the John Maudgridge Snowden Allison Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Inventory
  - General and collected correspondence
    - Thiers, Adolphe (1797-1877):
      - Signed, autographed letter to Don Philippe Gautani [?], 1838 August 3 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Signed, autographed letter to M. Pingaud, with envelope, 1868 January 15 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Signed, autographed letter to M. Rabit, with envelope, 1858 October 31 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Copies of two letters to M. Rouchon-Guiges, 1877 July 16, 17 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Signed, autographed letter to the prefect of a department, 1832 October 21 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Signed letter to the author of a work on ceramic art, 1850 March 27 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Signed, autographed letter to a general [name not given], undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Signed, autographed letter to unnamed correspondent, 1862 May 15 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Signed, autographed letter to unnamed correspondent (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Miscellaneous original documents, 1792, 1793, 1818 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Lectures on France (Box 7)
  - Essays, Articles, Book Reviews (Box 8)
  - Student exam papers in Yale courses (Box 9)
  - Student essays submitted to Professor Allison (Box 10–12)
  - Lecture notes: "Three Fundamental Characteristics of the French" (Box 13)
  - History lecture notes and historiography (Box 14)
  - Lecture notes (Box 15)
  - History 32 lectures (Box 16)
  - History 140 lectures (Box 17–18)
  - Card Files: Notes on French History, Bibliography for French History (Box 19)
  - Folio containing documents signed by Louis XVI, 1786 Jun 22 (Box 20)